<resources>
    <string name="app_name">GetVehicle</string>
    <string name="title_activity_splash_screen">SplashScreenActivity</string>
    <string name="dummy_button">Dummy Button</string>
    <string name="dummy_content">DUMMY\nCONTENT</string>

    <!--menu items-->
    <string name="home">Home</string>
    <string name="cars">Cars</string>
    <string name="bikes">Bikes</string>
    <string name="others">Others</string>
    <string name="update_profile">Update Profile</string>
    <string name="logout">Logout</string>

    <!--navigation drawer-->
    <string name="nav_open">Open</string>
    <string name="nav_close">Close</string>
    <string name="mileage">Mileage</string>
    <string name="engine">Engine</string>
    <string name="location">Location</string>
    <string name="model_name">Model Name</string>
    <string name="fuel_type">Fuel Type</string>
    <string name="petrol">Petrol</string>
    <string name="overview">Overview</string>
    <string name="category">Category</string>
    <string name="subcategory">SubCategory</string>
    <string name="seatCount">Seat Count</string>
    <string name="transmission">Transmission</string>
    <string name="bootSpace">Boot Space</string>
    <string name="groundClearance">Ground Clearance</string>
    <string name="reviews">Reviews</string>
    <string name="ratings_and_reviews">Ratings and Reviews</string>
    <string name="rating_out_of">%.1f/%.1f</string>
    <string name="km_per_liter">kmpl</string>
    <string name="cost_per_day"><b>\u09F3</b> %d per day</string>
    <string name="about">About</string>
    <string name="profile">Profile</string>
    <string name="login">Log in</string>
    <string name="user_name">User Name</string>
    <string name="user_email">user@email.com</string>
    <string name="my_booking">My booking</string>
    <string name="about_details">Welcome to GetVehicle, your one-stop destination for renting vehicles for personal use. Our platform offers a wide variety of vehicles, from cars and motorcycles to RVs and boats, to meet your individual needs and preferences.\n\nOur mission is to provide an easy and seamless rental experience, allowing you to focus on the excitement and joy of driving and exploring. Whether you\'re planning a weekend getaway, a road trip with friends, or simply need a reliable vehicle to get around town, GetVehicle has got you covered.\n\nWe take pride in our commitment to exceptional customer service, providing you with the highest level of support throughout the entire rental process. Our team of experienced professionals is available 24/7 to assist you with any questions or concerns you may have.\n\nAt GetVehicle, we prioritize safety and reliability above all else. We thoroughly inspect and maintain all of our vehicles to ensure they meet the highest standards of quality and safety. Plus, our transparent pricing and user-friendly platform make it easy to find and book the perfect vehicle for your needs.\n\nThank you for choosing GetVehicle as your trusted partner in vehicle rental. We look forward to helping you find your next adventure on the road.</string>
</resources>